Welcome the fuck back.
Deadwood: The Movie is a western, drama film directed by Daniel Minahan.
Follow the 10-year reunion of the Deadwood camp to
celebrate South Dakota's statehood.
Former rivalries are reignited, alliances are tested and old wounds are reopened, as all are
left to navigate the inevitable changes that modernity and time have wrought.
Seth Bullock, played by Timothy Olyphant.
Al Swearengen, played by Ian McShane.
Alma Ellsworth, played by Molly Parker.
Trixie, played by Paula Malcomson.
Dan Dority, played by W. Earl Brown.
Charlie Utter, played by Dayton Callie.
Deadwood: The Movie is a 2019 American Western television film directed
by Daniel Minahan and written by David Milch for HBO.
It is a continuation of the television series of the same name, which was
created by Milch and ran for three seasons from 2004 to 2006.
The film reunites the majority of the show's large ensemble cast, including Timothy Olyphant, Ian McShane,
Molly Parker, Paula Malcomson, John Hawkes, and Gerald McRaney, and premiered on May 31, 2019.
The tone is emotional.